Contact: turkision@gmail.com
Thanks, brother.
Well, Ahmet Bey... As we talked.
Nothing should be deficient.
We ordered 2000 pitchers.
-Right? Well..
-Yes.
Some may be broken on
the way. Load some more.
-I can pay for them.
-As you order, Ayhan Agha.
Work never waits then.
I should go.
You can go. Stay safe.
Beys, welcome. Do you have any wishes?
-Do you cook human flesh, innkeeper?
-Oh my...
Bring lamb for each of us.
I don't have that much.
-Bring whatever you have then.
-Of course my Bey.
That's true. Mongolians tried
to take Osman Bey captive.
-And they lost their heads.
-What was his name?
Akcelasun or whatever. Their commander.
He threw that dog's head to Yakup Bey's feet.
Did the boys also play with the head, ha?
We shouldn't let even their
heads touch our feet, brother.
They probably showed
the head around on a spear.
I wish we had been there. So
we could have killed some nokers.
Warriors, why do you talk the dead's behind?
Even in the dinner table?
They are just dead now.
Just eat your food quietly.
-You are doing wrong.
-We miss slaughtering Mongolians.
They tortured us a lot. We want battle!
Do you want to kill Mongolians so bad?
We really do.
-We pray for it every time.
-You have good hearts.
Great Mergen, make them hear Erlik Khan.
They are the men we were
expecting. They'll stir up a big trouble.
-Be ready.
-Things will go crazy, Master Gera.
Mongolians!
Spare him.
You wanted to slaughter Mongolians.
Tengri (Turkish-Mongolian God) heard you.
I'm Karacelasun.
I came to avenge my brother.
Just be careful.
We are their master.
Nobody can stand against us.
Just hear me.
The arrow to touch you will burn my heart.
You are my only precious in this
world. We are one body, brother.
We are. Our parents are the same.
We were born at the same time.
I have brother to ruin their
world if something happens to me.
I'm not worried.
I swear I'll ruin their world, brother.
My brother.
Show me the enemies around.
My Bey, Mongolians in the east.
They've surrounded our borders.
They must have taken action after
the moves we made against them.
What else?
Byzantine in the west. To attack,
they are waiting for us to stumble.
They won't stop either. We
took their castles from them.
-What else?
-My Bey.
This spot is the land of Germiyan.
Since we canceled our loyalty,
they've seen us as an enemy.
They are just rivals not enemy, Bayindir Bey.
Muslims should never be
enemies against each other.
If they fall into carelessness,
they can be enemies, son.
If they convince the beys and
show us as the enemy against them,
...in this huge sea you see,
...we will remain like a small boat.
You always say those on the right
way are always alone and on their own.
Yes, they are.
Now show me another enemy.
Traitors among us.
Those who look like
friends to us and our land.
As you see, we are stuck here.
We are just like a wounded wolf.
The wounded wolf has nothing to
lose, my Bey. He attacks for his life.
So will we. We will attack.
-Bayindir.
-My Bey.
You will never get off the
tails of the traitors among us.
You have been after Ayhan Agha for long.
But you could find nothing. Speak now.
My Bey, Ayhan Agha has
been managing to get rid of me.
We got rid of me in Sogut
lastly. But I know where to start.
With Allah's will, I will find.
Thank you, thank you.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Increase the numbers of
patrols against Mongolians.
If an army comes, we should
know and attack accordingly.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Sons.
-My Bey.
-You two will go to the frontier market.
Keep your eyes on the
house of Germiyan all the time.
-As you order, my Bey.
-We will be hard on them, my Bey.
Thank you.
We won't stop, but continue the conquests.
We will attack Byzantine so
they won't be able to try to rise.
Konur, go to the headquarters at dawn.
Take the Bannerless with
you. Start the preparations.
As you order, my Bey.
We will see who stands beside us...
...and who doesn't.
We fight for Allah's
consent not for human desire.
May Allah bless our fight.
-Aameen, my Bey.
-Aameen.
Turkish soldiers are standing
in the yard, Karacelasun.
-Who are you?
-I'm a merchant.
That's what everybody thinks I am.
Do not lie to me.
My brother died because of your lies.
I am his executioner. You
knew we were mongols.
You foresee the trouble.
Who are you?
I am above you all, mongol.
I am the mighty Rome.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
I know you came for vengeance.
I was waiting for you.
Karacelasun.
We either die together or fight together.
We want the same heads, crusader.
-I am glad to hear that.
-You're just glad being alive.
You will give me your expert
soldiers. They will now how to hide.
My men are excellent fighters.
They are also very good at hiding.
Now you will tell me.
Where can I hit Osman,
Yakup, beys and their loved ones.
I will tell you with pleasure.
Where you will hit Osman and his loved ones.
Ladies sent word, there are some
potential brides at frontier marketplace.
Let us see them first thing in the morning.
Our sons have fallen for different people.
I don't know if what we do is alright.
I know Bala, I know. However..
Holofira can't be a bride
to us. You also know this.
She can not handle this state
dream. Her religion is different.
She is also very religious. She
grew up in palaces, she is fragile.
-She can not handle our load.
-Of course she can’t.
What about Orhan? What if he
oppose this, what will we do then?
My Orhan won't stand
against her mother for a girl.
-However, it will be hard.
-Of course it will be hard.
Love is the greatest feeling
our Rabb has granted to us.
However, our sons can
not show weakness to that.
What is important is the state,
Orhan will understand this as well.
However, my brother
wants it, mother. I can see it.
My brother is in love
with Holofira very much.
Love is important my daughter.
But state is more important.
I know Orhan. We will
find a suitable bride for sure.
Mother Bala, do you also not
want Gonca Hatun as a bride?
Gonca? To Alaeddin?
I was going to tell you that. I believe..
Alaeddin and Gonca loves each other.
However, Mother Bala
does not trust Saadet Hatun.
Of course Saadet can
not be trusted, however..
Gonca is a good girl. What will you do?
For now, I will observe.
If they really love each other..
Then I won't stand against them.
Of course there would be a way.
Let me go and check my brothers.
It seems they have a lot
more to worry about, a lot.
Quickly my daughter, you can go.
My brothers, you are sleepwalking.
Did you say something sister?
I'm saying, a while back..
While you are not at the palace. I
caught Gonca Hatun at your room.
She was looking for a room so to say.
You are always under
these kind of situations, sister.
You also told my mother about Gonca, right?
Are you going to deny it? I
know how you look at her, brother.
Fatma is right. Alaeddin..
Can you not tell me as well? So brother?
Look at me.
Are you really..
It will stay between us though do you swear?
I won't tell anyone. However, Fatma..
-I can not trust much.
Really brother?
Really? When did I do such a thing?
You never did something like that.
Do you ever do something like that?
Look here. How he has become
after hearing hatuns name.
He is already in love.
My heart and my mind
tells different things, brother.
Brother, this is love.
You will hear your heart, not your mind.
Now tell me. Do you love this Gonca Hatun?
Come on brother.
If you ask about my heart..
I do.
However, if you ask about my mind..
When we talk about love..
Mind is nothing but a tool.
I got my answer.
-Thank you.
-Don't..
Do not do it like my brother Orhan.
-What does it mean?
-Look here.
What about me?
Even the newborn babies will
know about my love to Holofira.
Tomorrow..
I will propose to Holofira.
What are you saying, brother?
It fits to my brother!
Tell me. When will you talk to Gonca Hatun?
-Brother.
-You need to be quick.
Or you will have to marry
with whoever our mothers find.
Look, you've heard Fatma.
First, I need to be sure about Gonca.
GERM1YANOGLU S1N1R1 / PAZAR
Osman Bey says...
...the one who is under a
shadow cannot have a shadow.
He took his allegiance back.
He doesn't know that when one is
not under the shadow of Germiyan...
...let alone growing, he cannot even survive.
Let Mongols slap them
first, let Byzantine hurt them...
Then he will understand.
It will happen, Mehmet. All
of those things will happen.
Once they hear that he left us...
...they will start attacking
them like mad dogs.
Don't you dare...
No one will show mercy.
No one will pity on them.
We cannot show mercy on traitors, my Bey.
Don't worry.
Mehmet! Inform the Bannerless.
Osman will want them as well
now. They must wait for the right time.
We will weaken Osman well enough first.
Yes father.
-Kanyumaz! -My Sultan.
-Send messengers.
I want all Beys to visit me.
They will all arrive in the frontiers
marketplace as soon as possible, my Sultan.
Not in the frontiers marketplace, Kanyumaz.
I want all Beys...
...to come to Kutahya, to my palace.
I will want them to present their submission.
I will not let them disappoint
me like Osman did.
Therefore, they will see me in my palace...
...with all my strength.
Attacking Kite is not a good move, Konur Bey.
If we are going to attack...
...we must attack villages nearby first.
We must plunder there.
We are not plunderers, Demir Boga (ironbull).
We are fighting for its people to be
treated with our justice and find peace.
Trying to attack Kite while
they are waiting for us...
...will put our lives in danger, Konur Bey.
Let's walk to Atranos.
GurDogan. (Strong Hawk)
Look...
Look at Atranos' roads.
Walking to Atranos before
taking Kite means killing our men.
When the soldiers of Kite
come to Atranos to help...
...these rocks will be our graves.
It is our duty to plan the moves for a fight.
We are not raiding caravans. Know your place.
Osman Bey is coming!
We will walk to Kite. Prepare the Bannerless.
Gurdogan... How long are
we going to obey them, huh?
Look at the situation we are in
on the way we set out for freedom.
We will turn our backs on them...
...in their hardest times...
...when they need us the most.
Konur, are the preparations all done?
Tell me what you did.
-Everything is ready, my Bey.
Where are you going?
Ya Allah!
We never let bandits step on our lands!
A little man with such bravery, huh?
But you have no bravery...
Come!
Gurbuz! Brother!
Hasan!
Save Gurbuz!
Gurbuz!
Do I have to crush your skull now...
..or should I drink your blood?
Alps! We are going back! Come on!
I will come for you all!
GERMIYANOGULLARI BORDER
BORDER MARKET
Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you.
All bride-to-be girls are in the marketplace.
Let me see them from a distance first.
My son... Where is Orhan?
I don't know,
Malhun mother.
Don’t you know? My brother...
What happened? Are you
hiding something from me?
Did Orhan...
-He will come.
He must be busy right now.
Let's see the girls first, then he
can come and meet them, huh?
I cannot silence myself,
brother. Isn't there a cure for that?
There is. There is.
Let's go to the palace first.
Then my brother will show you that cure.
So? Will you talk to Gonca Hatun?
Would I ever give you a secret, sister?
-Brother!
I will die of curiosity! Brother!
Orhan... What are you doing here?
I was looking for you.
You raided my caravan when you last did that.
And you always remember
the worst, Lord's daughter.
But I will make you forget
all your bad memories now.
How will that happen?
-I will take you somewhere.
Will you come with me?
I have to go to the marketplace. I am late.
-You will not be late, Holofira.
When you see the place we will go,
you will thank me for taking you there.
Orhan...
You will not stop, huh? Gokmen...
Wait for me here.
-Yes my Shahzade.
Where are we going?
You will see when we go there. Be patient.
Konur tell me... Is the
way to Bursa closed now?
Two caravans were hit, my Bey. One
of them had weapons and equipment...
..the other one was
carrying supplies. The way of
Iznik was surrounded
starting from the mountains.
-No support units can come from there, my Bey.
-We will move as soon as possible.
Mongols are behind us. Or else...
..we will feel the dagger behind us before
we are able to turn our faces to the east.
Kite is not strong enough, my Bey...
But we have been stronger before as well.
We can defeat them with a sudden attack.
As Alps attack the right-wing, the
Bannerless will attack the left-wing.
What happened?
Gurbuz? What happened?
My Bey, Mongols were here.
They attacked one caravan.
We attacked behind them
but we couldn't succeed.
We're all right but Gurbuz
brother is not well, my Bey.
What are you saying? Gurbuz?
You'll be all right.
Take him to the infirmary now.
Alps, come on. Bismillah.
Alps and Bannerless ones will be with you.
-You'll be leading them all, Konur.
-Yes, my Bey.
Alps will come with me!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER
BORDER MARKET
Ayse Hatun.
She’s very talented.
She's her father's favorite.
No, I know that girl. She's spoiled.
She can't handle being a hatun of a bey.
What are we going to do Malhun?
You don't like any one of them.
Not that I don't like them. Wife of our child
will also be the mother of the state.
The state is not a place to mess around.
-Yes, I know that.
-Move on then.
Malhun Hatun, Bala Hatun, welcome.
Let me pour you some sherbet.
Thank you, daughter. We have a
lot to do. We'll visit another time.
Come, visit our shop. Come on in.
We don't want it, daughter.
We don't have time.
Look at her. You can see it, right?
She’s trying to make us like her.
Everyone heard that
we are looking for a bride.
Young girls are excited.
You're right.
Only this one left. Aysima Hatun.
Her name comes from her beauty.
She's pretty beautiful, Praise be!
See? She saw us but she
didn't approach as others.
It's clear that she is decent.
She knows why we are looking
at her and she's embarrassed.
So, what about this girl?
Aysima Hatun was one of the
first to open a stall in this market.
They are looking for girls for Shahzades.
-How did you get it mother?
-How do you think?
That tiny woman standing
next to them is matchmaker.
Go around the stalls, Ulgen.
Sure.
Osman broke his oath.
Approach Alaeddin further more, Gonca.
Mother. They put us into the dungeon.
Don't you remember how were we?
We are all right, Gonca.
Approach Alaeddin.
Let's find out Osman's secrets.
Hurry up. Today
they are looking for girl for Orhan,
they will be looking
around for Alaeddin soon.
For Alaeddin?
Ah, mother!
It's for you, the daughter of the Lord.
Come on, here.
You have surprised me a lot, Shahzade.
I wouldn't expect it from you.
I'll surprise you lot more, Holofira.
There’s one more thing.
Look at Shahzade Orhan.
You know too many tricks.
Lotus flower.
It's not like any other flower.
It's pretty hard to get.
Just like you.
Orhan.
It is so beautiful.
You know that it lives in the water, right?
It dies if you try to
plant it under the soil.
I know that.
And I do everything to keep it alive.
Do you know, Holofira?
That how much I love you?
Knowing it is not enough, Orhan.
It is, Holofira. It is.
But I want to know too. Is my love for you...
...mutual?
Is it not?
Your mother does not want me, Orhan.
And you can't go against your mother
for anyone.
You're right. I wouldn't go
against my mother for anyone.
But you...
...you are not anyone, daughter of the Lord.
You're dreaming, Orhan.
You will not be able to
go against your mother.
There will be a war between you and
your mother as soon as I say yes to you.
I cannot be the reason for this.
I can't.
-Come on, Andra.
-Holofira.
So you say that...
...if I convince my mother
if my mother says yes...
...you'll marry me?
We'll talk about it when it happens.
Oh, the daughter of the Lord.
Holofira will not be yours, Orhan.
I'll never let that happen.
Praise be! Praise be!
Your stall is in order.
I can't see anyone else. Do you
handle these things all by yourself?
I'm doing it all by myself. I can't entrust
the labor of my household to someone else.
Aysima, I know you and your family.
You know why I'm here, right?
I know. You're looking
for bride for your son.
I want you to meet with my son Orhan.
What do you think, daughter? Do you want it?
Brother. I'm so curious.
I swear I'll not say it.
Tell me brother, come on.
No. You cannot make me talk, sister.
They forgot about me
even before they get married.
I'll be ruined if they get married.
be ruined.
Trickster Hatun, where are you going?
We're going to practice, my Shahzade.
-You mind your own business.
-Oh, look at that.
Yes. You mind your business, Doctor.
-Let's go, Cerkutay.
If someone gets hurt
...you will need a doctor.
Yes, Cerkutay?
No, I can't hurt Gonca
Hatun. She is so beautiful.
She is.
Of course, she is.
Cerkutay Alp.
How about Scholar comes
with us? What do you say?
Well, he can. Let's go.
We don't have much time. Let's go!
Stop. Stop!
Stop.
There was an ambush. Be careful.
This is a trap, alps. Alps!
They laid traps everywhere. Draw your swords.
They may have laid traps everywhere. Careful.
It seems Mongolian dogs didn't come
here only to attack the caravan, my Bey.
Obviously not. They
attacked. But the cart isn't here.
They intend to hide in the cart.
Where do you think they will attack, my Bey?
They got the cart. Look.
The food is here.
The gold is here.
They're going to attack. Tell me now.
What is that cart appropriate for?
For the market.
They're going to attack the frontier market.
Turahan!
-Turahan, are you alright?
-I'm good, my Bey.
-Aykurt, are you alright?
-I'm fine, Boran Bey.
-Alps, is everyone alright?
-We have a wounded one, my Bey.
-Take him to the heal house immediately.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Are you alright, brother?
-I'm good, my Bey.
They are one step ahead of us.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Gonca Hatun!
Take the shahzade down! Come on!
-You put me in the dungeon.
-And you call me a hypocrite.
Are you not? Ha?
-You keep confusing me.
-Is that why you are so angry?
Did you think I would forget?
Ha?
-You put me in the dungeon for no reason.
-I know you didn't forget.
But you know we had to.
If it were up to your father...
Don't talk about my father!
You put both my brother's
and Orhan Bey's lives in danger.
But we saved them didn't we?
Trickster Hatun.
Don't you underestimate me, Scholar.
Stop! We are training here not killing.
The winner for this training is
Gonca Hatun, my Shahzade.
Now you'll do whatever Gonca Hatun says.
Oh really? But that's not what
you said in the beginning, Cerkutay.
This is the rule of the game my Shahzade.
You say so?
Fine.
What do you wish Trickster Hatun?
Cerkutay.
If our Shahzade is a scholar...
...and a bookworm,
...read a poem for us then.
"What comes from you is gracious
to me. Either a rosebud or a thorn.
It's either life or a shroud.
Both your fire and light are gracious.
Both your sorrow and blessing are gracious."
You wait here, dear.
I'll introduce you to my son.
Orhan, welcome.
-Mother.
I found a girl for you. Let
me introduce you to her.
-Mother.
-Orhan, do what I say. Come on.
Holofira.
-You don't look well.
-I'm good.
I'm good.
Very good.
Aysima, this is my son Orhan.
Aysima is dealing with this
stand, handling things on her own.
Orhan, I'm talking you.
Nice to meet you, Aysima.
Where are you coming from?
Which stand are you taking the goods too?
It's all written here.
We've brought Erlik Khan's wrath for you!
Nokers, attack!
Alps, take position!
-Come on, go to the tent!
-Hurry up!
-Fatma bring the swords, quickly!
-Malhun Hatun!
Mother, you protect the people.
I will respond to them, quickly!
Fatma protect yourself!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay! My son!
Cerkutay is missing. Our son is missing.
-Cerkutay!
-Son!
Cerkutay!
My son! Cerkutay!
-Cerkutay!
-Get inside!
Gonca!
-Gonca are you alright!
-I am alright.
-Malhun Hatun!
-Aysima!
Aysima!
Holofira!
Aysima! Aysima!
Quickly get up!
Cerkutay Alp is coming!
Where is Cerkutay!
Cerkutay!
Where are you?
-My son! Son!
-Cerkutay!
Break it.
Break it from here.
Am I becoming a martyr, father?
No, no, you are alright.
You are alright my valiant.
You will be alright, hold on.
You are alright, my valiant.
I will come back for you soon.
Fall back.
Do not let them get away!
KUTAHYA
GERMIYAN PALACE
The fate of the Turks and
muslims in these lands..
Is bound to the decision that
will be made in the council tonight.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
Grandness shows power.
Rugs and other gifts..
Shall be ready fit to our name.
As you command, my Sultan.
Those who can not praise
Osman's council enough..
Will understand that they are in
the presence of a Sultan tonight.
They will decide accordingly as well.
Kanyumaz.
Tell alps to be ready..
To act in any case.
This is the place, my Bey.
So this is the house of Hasan
Aga you have been saying.
He hasn't been seen after the ambush.
Alright, you go on your duty.
You think they are hiding in here, bey?
Let us strike at night. Let me ask for help.
No. No one will know.
Only Allah and I shall know
what I will do.
You stay near me, that's enough.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER
BORDER MARKET
Cerkutay, can you hear me valiant?
He can not.
He can not!
My Shahzade, do something.
Do something my Shahzade.
He will be alright.
Be alright, my valiant.
Be alright. Get up my
valiant, we will do great things.
I will teach you how to be an
alp. My valiant come on, Cerkutay..
Ulgen, don't overshadow your
heart. We will pray and aid him.
-With Allah's permission, he'll be alright.
-I hope so.
Gonca Hatun.
Put this to the wounds, Gonca Hatun.
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
-You think this will work, Alaeddin Bey?
-If Allah permits...
...it will work.
It has to work.
What do you mean it has to Alaeddin Bey?
Aren't you a healer?
I am trying to find the poison Mehmed Bey.
I have to find it to prepare antidote.
Then hurry Alaeddin Bey.
Do not think that this ambush
has nothing to do with you.
You are the ones ruining unity.
Mehmed Bey.
Mehmed Bey, this is
neither the place nor the time.
Don't talk like that without knowing.
Bala, Alaeddin tell me what happened.
It is not good father. Not good.
My Bey.
My dear.
My Bey, do something.
My Bey, my son is dying in front
of me, he just called me father.
Will he say it again? Will
he say it again, my bey?
Cerkutay.
No, don't say it like that.
Cerkutay does not give up
that easily. Right my dear?
Look at me. Don't ever overshadow yourself.
Do you hear me?
Look at me.
Cerkutay.
Won't die.
-Cerkutay.. will not die.
-Will not die.
Incompetent fools!
- Secret House -
When I looked at your body, your hair...
...your huge bodies...
...and your words...
...I thought you were real men!
Can your pathetic eyes
see me at first glance?
Ilkhanate is way more
powerful than your Rome.
There are different types of poison.
Do you think there is an antidote
for the poison in their blood?
Do not underestimate your enemy Karacelasun.
You have the smell of pride in your breath.
They got rid of us many times.
If you are so small
everyone looks big in your eyes, crusader.
I didn't attack the marketplace,
I spread terror among them.
I spat fire on them.
They'll wake up in fear every morning.
They will never be able to get better.
I don't care about what you did to them!
You said vengeance! Where is it?
Osman and Yakup are still alive.
What are you going to do now, Karacelasun?
Commander, Yakup Bey are
gathering with other Turkish Beys.
Our Nokers are searching we'll locate them.
Now we know what to do, crusader.
I promise by the presence of Jesus Christ,
we'll do it.
Is your bandage pressing hard,
do you want me to loosen it?
Astagfirullah Malhun Hatun,
I don't want to bother you.
You were so brave.
You risked your life for me,
of course it wouldn't bother me.
If you hadn't jumped in front of me
this wound would have been mine.
I'd do it again.
I’d never think about it, Malhun Hatun.
Thank you, my beautiful girl.
Come on, get some rest.
Malhun Hatun, Osman Bey is
waiting for you at the council.
KUTAHYA
GERMIYAN PALACE
In the 99 Names of Allah Almighty
Who strengthened us and our country
for Whose cause we gave our lives,
open the council.
BismillahirRahmanirRahim.
The council has been gathered for conquest.
We have gathered in the palace
to confirm our well-known power.
Now, Beys. Each one of you
will take out your troops.
We'll move towards Byzantium.
Isn't Osman Bey here?
Osman Bey is drawing Mongols towards us.
He's acting on his own.
Furthermore, he withdrew his oath.
He has no place in the council anymore.
We shouldn't waste a brave
man like Osman Bey so easily.
If any one of you have objections
go and get ruined with him.
When it is about conquest,
if someone tries to take sides
I'd doubt the love of holy war in his heart.
Now, Beys. Each one of you
will unite under my banner.
Altogether.
We will make conquests together.
Are you with me?
-We are with you, Sultan Yakup.
We are with you, but...
But what? Karesi Bey?
You say that Osman drew Mongols towards us
but in the meantime you
plan conquests in West.
Are we going to be able
to fight on both sides?
What are we going to do if
Mongols come towards us?
Whoever cut the head will pay the price.
Mongols are not our problem for now.
So we will not get involved?
Did I cut that head, Karesi Bey?
This was not Osman's
first and it will not be the last.
We have saved him enough.
We will make conquests. We
will take everything Byzantium has.
With the power we gain
from it, we will turn to East,
to Konya.
Mongols are the problem
of tomorrow, not today.
Now, Beys. Send messengers to your lands.
All of the troops will unite under my banner.
We will ruin the infidels.
Our first target is Izmir.
Kanyumaz.
Come on, enjoy your food.
BismillahirRahmanirRahim.
Instead of attacking altogether
why are they attacking behind shadows?
They tried attacking
altogether many times, my Bey.
But we defeated them every time.
Orhan is right. If they come
towards us with an army, we will unite.
Which shield can stop the
arrow coming from a shadow?
Then why are they targeting
Frontier Marketplace?
They want to spread fear, my Bey.
We are not afraid, it's alright,
but what about the people?
If they attack the marketplace today,
they'll attack infirmary or medrese tomorrow.
Then there will be fear in
the hearts of all of the mothers.
Fear is like a finger-grass in Muslim soil.
It never greens.
But if they try to make it green
we will never let them do that.
They know it very well.
They will not stop after the
marketplace raid, my Bey.
Right. They want to ruin us.
What’s the target now?
Or who?
Their target is clear.
The ones on the top.
Me and Beys.
And Yakup Bey.
Come on.
My father entrusted the marketplace
to me but I couldn't protect it.
I'll ruin those embarrassed
me against Orhan...
Calm down son.
They are not like anyone
else we've seen before.
They knew that your father is away
and they attacked the marketplace.
Maybe they were going to
attack my father, brother?
There's a blessing in every harm.
Tell me, where is Yakup Bey?
Who are you to enter our
tent without permission?
Where is Yakup Bey?
Stop, Mehmed!
What are you going to do with Yakup Bey?
Yakup Bey is the reason why
they raided the marketplace.
Tell me... -Osman...
My father is with the Beys.
He is not alone like you. Don't worry.
Mehmet Bey! Behave yourself,
or I will rip your heart out.
My son... Stay back.
Son..
It is not a regular army.
They can enter Yakup Bey's
100 thousand horsemen...
...and kill him, and you cannot
understand who did it and how.
Thus, tell me. Where is Yakup Bey?
Yakup Bey left to stop
you from dissuading Beys...
...and ruining the conquests.
That's why he set the war council far away.
Now... you are using infidels' game to...
...learn where my Bey is.
If I go back with empty hands...
...only thing that will come to the
marketplace will be Yakup Bey's dead body.
Know that.
My Bey! My Bey! Osman Bey!
My son.. -My Bey...
The injured ones are dying one
by one. They are all poisoned.
What?
I tried everything!
But I couldn't find the antidote, my Bey.
My son...
Cerkutay! Won't Cerkutay survive?
Cerkutay...
I am slowing it.
First, their veins get bigger.
Then their heart starts beating faster.
Those who have a deep wound die sooner...
...and the ones who are lightly
injured die slowly, my Bey.
My Allah, protect our children.
Send news to all
cities around us!
I want most talented doctors to
be in the frontiers marketplace!
Gonca! Gonca!
Gonca! Gonca! What happened?
-Gonca Hatun...
Gonca! Gonca... What happened?
Come on, let's take her inside.
Come on... Slowly..
Gonca! My daughter.. -Slowly.
Gonca! -Brother..
Brother, pull yourself together!
The ointment., we need the ointment.
come.
If you gave that gold to Mongols with...
...your honour and glory, we
wouldn't be going through this.
I will kill you Osman!
My son... You are a strong valiant.
But... I am also patient.
Don't you test my patience.
My son..
Now tell me where your
father is. If you don't..
...all the pain we've suffered from...
...will only be the beginning of the
pain we will suffer from in the future.
Come on.
Tell me.
Search everywhere!
Are you sure, my Bey?
This is the only place we
do not know the owner of.
They should search everywhere.
I think something is here.
Bayindir Bey, we looked
everywhere. The house is clean.
It's clean, my Bey.
Allah Allah.. What are you doing?
Bayindir Bey?
What happened? -Ayhan Agha..
What happened? What are you doing here?
My Bayindir Bey..
How can I explain?
Alps... Go out, Alps.
My Bey, let me stay with you.
-I said go.
My Bayindir Bey, you are a talented Bey.
I am saying this with all my heart.
You found..
...what no one could know and find.
What are you saying, Ayhan Agha?
Oh well..
Come, Bayindir Bey.
Ayhan Agha... Do you hide your gold here?
A part of it, let's say. A little part of it.
May Allah give you more.
One cannot believe.
Although you were talented enough to...
...solve my secret...
...how could they attempt getting
rid of you with a single doubt?
That's why I am feeling sorry.
Do not worry about that, Ayhan Agha.
You should worry about
how you are going to answer...
...for all this gold and
money on the other side.
I had the same problem in the past.
I gave all of it to other
people and found peace.
Thanks to Allah.
My Bayindir Bey. This gold..
...is halal for me just like my
deceased mother's milk was.
Praise be.
But still, I am afraid.
That's another issue.
And about the questioning... The
actual people who need to give answers...
..are the ones who asked for...
...the head of a valiant like you...
...with a slander. I am
worried about them and
how they are going to
answer on the other side!
Heal... Heal him, my Allah..
Heal my son...
I have no One to ask
help from, except for You.
Peace be upon you.
Dervish Efendi.
May he recover soon. How is he?
They couldn't find the cure.
I am losing my son and I cannot do anything.
Everything that comes comes from Allah.
Now we are struggling with this difficulty...
...but there must be a reason.
He is Dhul Jalal-i Wal Ikram (The
One of Majesty and Benevolence)
He first warns with His Majesty...
...then He offers with His Benevolence.
We never know, He is the One Who knows.
What am I going to do with
this pain, Dervish Efendi?
I don't know what I am going to do.
Holy Quran says:
"And know that your
wealth and your children...
...are only a test...
...and that with Allah...
...is a great reward."
[8:28]
Children are one of...
...the biggest tests.
How am I going to resist?
How am I going to be patient?
By looking at those who...
...experienced the heaviest tests.
Prophets, Messengers...
For instance, Hadhrat Ibrahim (A.S.)...
He was tested with childlessness for years.
He resisted. Then Allah...
...gave him Hadhrat Ismael
(A.S.) and Hadhrat Ishak (A.S.).
But the test was not over. Hadhrat Ibrahim...
...had promised Allah that he
would sacrifice his son Ismael for Him.
Prophet Ibrahim (A.S.) was split
between Hadhrat Ismael (A.S.)...
...and the promise he gave to Allah.
And he surrendered against such a great test.
He was so surrendered...
...that he put the knife on the
neck of Hadhrat Ismael (A.S.).
And the test of Hadhrat Ismael (A.S.)---
...was to show loyalty to
the promise his father gave.
He was so faithful that..
...he put his neck on his father's knife.
You know what happened afterwards.
My Allah sent a ram from the sky as a gift.
First Jalaal, then Jamaal.
Hadhrat Jacob (A.S.)...
He was tested with the longing
of Hadhrat Joseph (A.S.)...
...and also the longing
of his other children.
He was patient. Then...
The messenger of Allah(PBUH).
Our Prophet who was sent
to the worlds as Allah's mercy.
He saw all his children die
except Hadhrat Fatimah (R.Ag).
He put them all in the graves.
Even he endured the suffering.
Prophets knew the life, all the gifts,
...the goods and even the children...
...came from Allah..
...and they would return to Him again.
Now you should follow
the path of Prophets now.
Pray with patience.
Don't you be one of those who cry out
Those who cry out against
the troubles have always lost.
Those who pray with patience
have always won in the both worlds.
Well, patience doesn't mean...
...just waiting with tears.
Well, we all pray.
The most appropriate
prayer is the prayer with effort.
It means... You demand the heal from Allah.
But you also need to seek
heal. Seek it inside you.
And to do this, you need
to remember yourself first.
Who were you?
Who was I?
I was Cerkutay.
Cer... an Alp.
I don't know about healing.
I'm not a doctor.
I'm not saying you are a doctor.
I'm saying... Just find yourself.
A child is a father's secret.
Look at your secret and find the truth.
The heal always lies within the truth.
Find it.
My brother sent this. He told you
to clean the wound and apply this.
How did she endure this pain for so long?
She doesn't talk.
She never talks to anyone.
She cures her own wounds.
My Allah, spare my child's life for me.
Amen.
Gonca will be alright,
Saadet Hatun. Don't be afraid.
With Allah's will, everybody will be
alright. We'll do whatever Alaaddin said.
You heard Alaaddin. He said no.
He said he can't find the cure.
Bala Hatun, what will I do now?
The cure comes from Allah.
We'll find it with Allah's will.
Kismet, her fever is going
up. Prepare water with vinegar.
We'll be ahead of them when the sun arises.
You'll be leading the
catapults. Gurbuz, Hasan.
We'll have alps here too.
Heathens will think we're
outnumbered and they will attack.
When they attack, the
Bannerless will show up.
We and the Bannerless
will fight from two directions.
Yes, we'll surround the heathens.
We're outnumbered but the
Bannerless will change everything.
I didn't like them at first but...
...they'll solve an issue.
Yes, we wouldn't be able to
conquer without the Bannerless.
I'm glad the Bannerless are with us.
We aren't with you anymore.
We've drawn back our loyalty to Osman Bey.
We're starting the conquest
shortly. Are you saying this now?
It doesn't matter when, Konur Bey.
This is our decision. Now you conquer...
-And we loot again.
-You say so?
Are you showing your gratitude to those
who saved you from the heathens like this?
By betraying, ha?
We owe nothing to anyone.
We could have just gone
without informing, but...
...we just wanted to act nobly.
Nobly?
Look at those noble men.
You said you didn't want to be killed with
a vile dagger instead of becoming a martyr.
Now I see..
You just deserve to be
killed with a vile dagger.
We have no place for the betrayer
and the heartless in Osman Bey's army.
Now get out of here.
What are we going to do now, Konur Bey?
What's the situation?
Bey, the bannerless left the army.
Alps are not enough as well.
I took the initiative and stopped the
conquest, Bey. Alps are in the quarters.
So he acted in his nature.
Just as we accepted. Whatever.
It's better then them leaving in the war.
You mean..
Kite is waiting for its conquest you say.
Tell me, what did you do
since you stopped the conquest.
I put some alps around the Kite.
I increased the scouts around.
And I put the skilled ones inside as a spy.
Conquest has stopped for now,
but preparations are being made.
There..
That is the principle
that will take us to victory.
Not stopping even if we're at halt.
-Now where are we going, Bey?
-Those who hit the marketplace and alps..
Are after Yakup Bey. They
can not hit him at the palace.
Since we haven't received any
news they will hit him on the road.
Alps, quickly.
Soon the scouts will inform us
about the place of Yakup and Beys.
Five of you.
You will be after Yakup and Beys.
Aren't the Beys together, Karacelasun?
Why aren’t all of your men going there?
Where are the rest of your men?
You crusaders..
Are knowing Turks for a
hundred, maybe two hundred years.
We know them for a thousand years, crusader.
They stayed alive like
this for all these years.
Even if they clash on the inside, they
always unite against the outer enemy.
Meaning?
Osman will come to save Yakup.
The others already trapped the roads.
These woods are ours.
They will be a grave for all of them today.
Commander, Yakup Bey and others..
They are on their way back.
They are waiting for the army.
Bayci.
Bring me that poison.
Today we become a scorpion for Turks.
Let's take their heads before army arrives.
My Sultan.
What news do you bring from Iznik?
There is hard work going
on in Iznik, my Sultan.
The people and the soldiers
around the castle retreat into the wall.
The Lord is guessing the outcome..
-And preparing, is that so?
-Since he is taking many precautions..
He must've asked for
reinforcements as well, Sultan Yakup.
There won't be anyone
coming for help except Bursa.
And before the army
arrives from Constantinople..
The city will fall already.
Beys.
I want your armies at Iznik walls..
After three days.
Okay, Bey.
With Allah's permission..
We will honor Iznik with Islam..
And stab our banner to infidel's chest!
May we prevail! Quickly!
Alps!
My Bey.
Don't fall. Are you alright?
Take the shields.
Bey..
-There are traps.
-Exactly.
-They know we went to Yakup Bey.
-Then let us move from another route, Bey.
The other roads that go to
Kutayha has hills, my Bey.
We do not have much time,
we will take the same route.
So take your shields. Come on now.
Thank you. Now..
Alps, we need to take the
Beys. We will take the Beys.
Or our land will perish. Even if
martyrdom is at the end of this..
We will walk. Quickly, help him.
Quickly.
Come on now.
Alps, watch ahead.
Quickly, quickly.
Alps. There is a trap ahead.
Quickly, this way, come.
From here.
Release the horses!
There are arrows everywhere, Bey.
-Alps, is everyone okay?
-We have two wounded, Bey.
Alps..
Seems it stopped. Let us move slowly.
Gather around.
We miss valiant enemies,
Bey. There are traps everywhere.
Valiants do not know us as
enemy. These are just dogs.
We have to reach the Beys
quickly. Bring the horses.
Quickly. Come on.
There will be a lot of blood.
The spirits of the trees..
Will feast with blood.
There will be blood of river, from dry lands.
They will experience Erlik Khan's wrath.
I will free my sibling's
soul, by having vengeance.
It will be the end of the Turks. Quickly.
My Sultan, these are our scout alps.
Alps, stay alert.
Alps! Stay alert!
My Sultan!
-Take cover!
-They are coming from everwhere!
Where are these arrows coming from?
Hang on!
Stay together!
When the smoke disappears, we will attack!
Come on! My Bey! Come on!
We are losing Alps one
by one. We cannot resist!
We will resist Karesi Bey! We will!
You forgot Ilkhanid's power!
You became rebels when you had a
leader. Now you will lose your heads!
You took my brother's head.
And I will take your heads
with me everywhere I go!
You cannot escape here you will die here!
Come on!
GERM1YANOGLU SIN1R1 / EC PAZAR
He called me father.
He will say it again, right, Ulgen?
-He will.
You will get better soon..
...I will do everything you say.
My lion..
My son..
We will organize your circumcision feast.
I will give you a horse.
Hang on. Resist, my valiant.
Don't be scared... He is like his father.
He ate all those meals, a single
arrow won't be enough to defeat him.
My Allah, let our son stay with us.
He is still burning, he
has a high temperature.
My Shahzade... Alaeddin Bey.
He is still burning.
His fever does not go down.
Ulgen Hatun. Keep putting
on water with vinegar.
My Shahzade..
For the consent of Allah please heal my son.
Cerkutay Bey... I will heal him.
I know the antidote of Mongols' poison.
But this is different...
This poison is different.
Be patient.
My Shahzade! My Shahzade!
Let's turn him on his side.
-Bismillah.
Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return."
No... It does not work.
Nothing works!
He will be alright.
My Allah, help us.
My beautiful daughter...
My Gonca..
My rosy Gonca..
Come on, open your eyes.
Come on, my beautiful daughter.
I failed.
I couldn't protect her, mother. I couldn't
protect my father's entrustment.
Mehmet!
Pull yourself together Mehmet.
Pull yourself together.
My sister... If something
happens to my sister, mother...
Nothing will happen to her.
Your sister will get better and stand up.
My one wing is injured and in blood, Mehmet.
If something happens to my
other wing, what am I going to do?
You will be strong and stand tall.
Saadet Hatun.
How is she?
She is still unconscious.
But she will wake up.
My beautiful daughter
will get better and stand up.
She will.
She is a brave woman. Gonca
Hatun is a fearless woman.
She is very strong. She
will get over this for sure.
Her mother's one and only
is strong, she is really strong.
Your firmness will make
her firm, Saadet Hatun.
Also, Alaeddin Bey is looking for a cure.
-Soon he will find it.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Thank you.
-Gonca, what happened?
-Saadet Hatun.
-Gonca.
-Sister.
-Gonca! Gonca!
-Let us take a look Saadet Hatun.
-Is she breathing?
-Turn her.
Is she breathing? Gonca? Gonca?
-Sister? Talk to me.
-Gonca?
Open it.
Is she breathing? Gonca?
Sister! Gonca!
Gonca?
-Gonca!
Say something! Gonca!
-Gonca! Gonca!
-Sister!
-Sister! Gonca!
-Gonca!
Ulgen. How is the child?
Don't cry. Be better so
he can be better as well.
We will pray together.
Cerkutay?
Cerkutay, something's happening.
Cerkutay.
Son? Son? Cerkutay?
What happened? What?
Son? Son.
-Cerkutay?
-He's not breathing.
-Alps!
Alps! Call Alaeddin, now!
Son? My son!
-Calm down, calm down.
-My son!
Cerkutay! Breathe, son!
My son! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Son! My son!
No, no, no!
No! My son!
My Cerkutay, my son, please breathe!
Cerkutay, breathe!
No, no, no! Son! Cerkutay!
Look, my son.
Cerkutay, breathe! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
What are we going to do?
The smoke is clearing out, attack!
Osman! You’ve come to death
before death comes for you.
I'll destroy all of your
cities to avenge my brother!
Your brother died you will die too.
My Bey! My Bey!
The death will be after you all the time.
I'll come back for you soon.
Anyone tries to destroy
Turks will end up dying!
Nokers, retreat!
Allah is the Greatest!
Alps! Go after them!
Candar Bey.
Candar.
Candar Bey was poisoned.
He passed away, my Bey.
Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return.
The swords used and arrows thrown...
They were all poisonous, my Bey.
Gonca! Gonca! Is she breathing?
-Sister! Gonca!
-Cerkutay, breathe!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay’
Contact: turkision@gmail.com